// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "What will 2+2 be ?",
    answer: "4",
    options: [
      "4",
      "1",
      "0",
      "-2"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "What will 12a + 26b -4b – 16a. Become after combining them",
    answer: "-4a + 22b",
    options: [
      "-4a + 22b",
      "0",
      "-26+2b",
      "12a+b"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Factor of 5x2 – 15x – 20 is ?",
    answer: "5(x-4)(x+1)",
    options: [
      "2(x+2)(2+x)",
      "5(x-4)(x+1)",
      "-2+2",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Factor of 16w3 – u4w3 is",
    answer: "w3(4 + u2)(2 + u)(2 - u).",
    options: [
      "w3(4 + u2)(4 - u2).",
      "w3(42 - ((u2)2).",
      "w3(4 + u2)(2 + u)(2 - u)",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which is greater than 4 ?",
    answer: "5",
    options: [
      "5",
      "-5",
      "-1/2",
      "-25"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Which is the smallest number among them ?",
    answer: "-1",
    options: [
      "-1",
      "-2",
      "-3",
      "-4"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 7,
    question: "What is 16x9=?",
    answer: "144",
    options: [
      "144",
      "100",
      "20",
      "None Of The Above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Angle which is less than 90° is called ?",
    answer: "Acute Angle",
    options: [
      "Obtuse Angle",
      "Acute Angle",
      "Reflex Angle",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Angle Which is bigger that is bigger than 90° is called ?",
    answer: "Obtuse Angle",
    options: [
      "Acute Angle",
      "Straight Angle",
      "Reflex Angle",
      "Obtuse Angle"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Who is the father of maths ?",
    answer: "Archimedes",
    options: [
      "Loocols Silo",
      "Archimedes",
      "Mark Zuckerberg",
      "Jeff Bezos"
    ]
  },
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];